{
    "id": "51ba5575deab40c3a3ecb926fd682c4f",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Space research has been growing by leaps and ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bounds",
                "fits",
                "starts"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The duty of space scientists is to …………………. the mysteries of the universe.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unravel",
                "identify",
                "disclose",
                "diagnose"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The government assured the Supreme Court that it has taken all steps to ………………….. the formation of the new state.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expedite",
                "extract",
                "accelerate"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ..................... of his statement are far-reaching.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "applications",
                "implications",
                "allusions",
                "consequences"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten your ..................... . number of pizza slices.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "allotted",
                "subscribed",
                "prescribed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Calumny",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "encomium",
                "veritable",
                "slander",
                "virtuous"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonyms of  Anathema",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blessing",
                "curse",
                "potent",
                "privileged"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Disparate",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Similar",
                "Dissimilar",
                "Ordinary",
                "Authentic"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Interdict",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Allow",
                "Approve",
                "Appreciate",
                "Prohibit"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Inveterate",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Chronic",
                "Irate",
                "Curable",
                "Corrigible"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}